Richard Scarry Papers 1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993
  - The Great Steamboat Mystery, 1975
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 842)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 843)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 844)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 32 and back cover?), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 845)
  - Huckle's Book, 1979
    - Pencil artwork (9 pieces), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 846)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 847)
  - The Just Right Work Book, 1990
    - Black and white artwork (12 pieces), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 384)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 385)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 386)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 387)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 388)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 389)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 390)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 391)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 392)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 393)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 394)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 395)
    - Black and white and color separations (back cover), ca. 1990 (Box OS:, Folder 396)
  - Lowly Worm Sniffy Book, 1978
    - Black and white separation and blueboard (front end page and title page), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 848)
    - Pencil art (pages 4-5), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 849)
    - Pencil art (pages 6-7), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 850)
    - Pencil art (pages 8-9), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 851)
    - Pencil art (pages 10-11), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 852)
    - Pencil art (pages 12-13), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 853)
    - Pencil art (pages 14-15), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 854)
    - Pencil art (pages 16-17), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 855)
    - Pencil art (pages 18-19), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 856)
    - Pencil art (pages 20-21), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 857)
    - Pencil art (pages 22-23), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 858)
  - Lowly Worm Car and Truck Book, 1983
    - Pencil art (12 pieces), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 859)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (cover), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 860)
    - Pencil art (cover), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 861)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (title page), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 862)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 863)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 864)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 865)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 866)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 867)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1983 (Box OS:, Folder 868)
  - Lowly Worm Word Book, 1981
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (cover), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 869)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 870)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 871)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 872)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 873)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 10-11), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 874)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 875)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 876)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 16-17), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 877)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 18-19), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 878)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 20-21), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 879)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 22-23), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 880)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 24-25), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 881)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 26-27), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 882)
  - Lowly's Schoolbag, 1987
    - Original black and white artwork (3 pcs.), ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - Lowly Learns about Colors, original black and white artwork (13 pcs.), ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
    - Lowly Learns about Colors, layout sketches, set A, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
    - Lowly Learns about Colors, layout sketches, set B, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
    - Lowly Learns His ABCs, layout sketches, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
    - Lowly Learns His ABCs, original black and white artwork (12 pcs.), ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
    - Lowly Learns to Count, layout sketches, set A, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
    - Lowly Learns to Count, layout sketches, set B, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
    - Lowly Learns to Count, original black and white artwork (12 pcs.), ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
    - Lowly Learns Words, layout sketches, ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
    - Lowly Learns Words, original black and white artwork (13 pcs.), ca. 1987 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
  - Lowly Worm's Bath Book, 1984
    - Original artwork (7 pcs.), undated (Box 1:, Folder 39)
  - Lowly Worm Storybook, 1977
    - Original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
  - Lowly Worm Word Book, 1981
    - Layout sketch, ca. 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 41)
    - Original black and white artwork (13 pcs.), ca. 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 42)
  - Lowly's Schoolbag, 1987
    - Lowly Learns about Colors, color and black and white separations (pages 16-17), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 487)
    - Lowly Learns his ABCs, color and black and white separations (pages 4-5, 10-17), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 488)
    - Lowly Learns his ABCs, color and black and white separations (pages 18-29), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 489)
    - Lowly Learns to Count, color and black and white separations (pages 4-15), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 490)
    - Lowly Learns to Count, color and black and white separations (pages 16-29), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 491)
    - Lowly Learns Words, color and black and white separations (pages 16-29), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 492)
    - Lowly Learns Words, color and black and white separations (pages 4-15), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 493)
    - Original color artwork, exterior (3 pieces), ca.1987 (Box OS:, Folder 494)
  - "Maestro Mouse" series notes, undated (Box 1:, Folder 43)
  - Mix or Match Storybook, 1979
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (cover), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 883)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 2), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 884)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 3), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 885)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 4), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 886)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 5), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 887)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 6), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 888)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 7), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 889)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 8), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 890)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 9), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 891)
    - Black and white artwork (18 pieces), ca. 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 892)
  - Mr. Fixit and Other Stories, 1977
    - Paste-up dummy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 44)
  - Music Mouse's Animal Orchestra (unpublished)
    - Incomplete dummy with notes, ca. 1961 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
  - My First Word Book, 1986
    - Sketches (6 pieces), ca.1986 (Box OS:, Folder 894)
  - Noah's Ark (unpublished)
    - Incomplete sketch dummy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 46)
  - Numbers, preliminary drawings, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1302)
  - Peasant Pig and the Terrible Dragon, with Lowly Worm the Jolly Jester, 1980
    - Black and white acetate artwork (24 pieces), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 921)
    - Blueboard (cover), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 922)
    - Colored blueboard (cover), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 923)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 924)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 925)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 926)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 927)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 928)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 929)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 930)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 931)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 932)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 933)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 934)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 935)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 936)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 937)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 938)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 939)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 940)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 941)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 942)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 943)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 944)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 945)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1980 (Box OS:, Folder 946)
  - Pig Will and Pig Won't, 1984 (Box :)
    - Original black and white artwork (13 pieces), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1076)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1077)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1078)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1079)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1080)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1081)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1082)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1083)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1084)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1085)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 18), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1086)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 19), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1087)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 20), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1088)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 21-22), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1089)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 23), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 1090)
  - Please and Thank-You Book, 1973
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Sam the Smasher," page 1), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 947)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Sam the Smasher," page 2), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 948)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Tom the Terrible Tease"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 949)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Disobedient Dolly"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 950)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Messy Max"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 951)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Halibut"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 952)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Lowly the Polite Gentleworm," page 1), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 953)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Lowly the Polite Gentleworm," page 2), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 954)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Laughing Harry Hyena"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 955)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Terrible Tiffy and Awful Alfie"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 956)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Huckle's Garden"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 957)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Pig Won't and the Pie"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 958)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("The Egg Stealers"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 959)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Pig Will, Pig Won't," page 1), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 960)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Pig Will, Pig Won't," page 2), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 961)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Pig Will, Pig Won't," page 3), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 962)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Pig Will, Pig Won't," page 4), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 963)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Everyone is a Helper," page 1), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 964)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Everyone is a Helper," page 2), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 965)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Everyone is a Helper," page 3), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 966)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Everyone is a Helper," page 4), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 967)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Lowly Worm's Horrid Pests"), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 968)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Good Friends and Neighbors," page 1), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 969)
    - Preliminary layout drawings ("Good Friends and Neighbors," page 2), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 970)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 971)
    - Black and white and color separations (title page), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 972)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 973)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 974)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 975)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 976)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 977)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 978)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 979)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 980)
    - Color and partial black and white separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 981)
    - Color and partial black and white separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 982)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 983)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 984)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 985)
  - Postman Pig and His Busy Neighbors, 1978
    - Black and white sketches (17 pieces), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 902)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 903)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 1), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 904)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 905)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 906)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 907)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 908)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 909)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 910)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 911)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 912)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 913)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 914)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 915)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 916)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 917)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 918)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 919)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 32), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 920)
  - Random House press release on Scarry, ca. 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
  - Richard Scarry's Biggest Word Book Ever, 1985
    - Color and text separations (pages 1), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 495)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 1), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 496)
    - Color and text separations (pages 2), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 497)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 2), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 498)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 3), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 499)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 4), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 500)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 5), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 501)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 6), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 502)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 7), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 503)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 8), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 504)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 9), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 505)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 10), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 506)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 11), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 507)
    - Color, black and white, and text separations (pages 12), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 508)
    - Color separations (front cover), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 509)
    - Color and black and white separations (back cover), ca. 1985 (Box OS:, Folder 510)
  - Richard Scarry's Busiest People Ever, 1976
    - Sketches (pages 2-47), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 511)
    - Acetate artwork (10 pieces, pages 2-3, 24-25, 34-37, 46-47), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 512)
    - Blue board (pages 6), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 513)
    - Black and white contact sheet (pages 6), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 514)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 515)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 516)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 517)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 518)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 519)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 520)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 521)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 522)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 523)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 524)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 525)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 526)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 527)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 528)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 529)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 530)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 531)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 532)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 533)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover and title page), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 534)
    - Black and white and color separations (front end papers), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 535)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 536)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 537)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 538)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 539)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages ), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 540)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 541)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 542)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 543)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 544)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 545)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 546)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 547)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 548)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 549)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 550)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 551)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 552)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 553)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 554)
      Note: Pages 44-45 not included with the collection.
    - Black and white and color separations (back end papers), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 555)
  - Richard Scarry's Busy Houses, 1981
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (front cover), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 556)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 557)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 558)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 559)